totalbhakti.com 2016-11-27

# Totalbhakti.com a place for all spiritual person group togather with Online Bhajan Guru Videos Ramayana, Gita and Yatra Darshan Spiritual Person video yoga videos, meditation

Totalbhakti.com is committed to safeguarding the privacy of its on-line users\' Personal information. Please read the following policy to understand the rules and procedures followed by TBC (totalbhakti.com) in handling Personal information provided to us over the Internet. If you have further questions regarding our privacy policy please contact us via email.

** Information collection **

TBC (totalbhakti.com) collects the Personal information only from persons who contact us and voluntarily provide the information to us or that is given to us by various affiliated organizations that have your permission to share your Personal information. “Personal information” means your name, shipping/mailing address, telephone number, fax number, email address, etc.

** Use of Personal Information **  

1\. We use your personal information to respond to and fulfill requests for products and services including: Sending information about the activities of TBC (totalbhakti.com) and our affiliates. 

2\. Sending you our e-newsletters

** Disclosure of personal information to others**

1\. TBC\'s mailing list, including the Personal information we receive through the Internet, is never shared with any commercial organization and is never sold, rented or given to unrelated third parties. 

2\. TBC (totalbhakti.com) will disclose Personal information to third parties if we believe in good faith that the law requires us to do so.

** How we protect your personal information**

TBC (totalbhakti.com) database is protected from unauthorized access by a series of highly sophisticated software protection programs. Our secure server software provides protection for your Personal information. We encrypt all of your Personal information so that it cannot be read as the information travels over the Internet. Sensitive data is also encrypted while being stored on our server. Your Personal information is password protected with access only to those selected and authorized persons. TBC(totalbhakti.com) is not responsible for the privacy, terms of use or other policies of any other web site.

** Amendment of Policy**

TBC  (totalbhakti.com) reserves the right to amend this Privacy Policy any time. No individual notice of such changes will be provided but they will appear on the website in the form of a revised and newly dated Privacy Policy.
